

ifeogunderu@gmail.com | 08186051192

Oworonsoki, Lagos

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Knowledgeable individual with quality-driven and methodical approach to completing daily tasks and solving complex problems. Excellent communication and analytical abilities.

Experienced working with teams to produce impact, leading-edge websites that engage customers and deliver business results. Well-versed in design standards and user preferences.

SKILLS

HTML

JavaScript

CSS

Scss

React

Vue

Firebase

Photoshop

EXPERIENCE

Tech Intern

HNG LTD - Remote | June 2020 - July 2020

- · Resolved networking and connectivity issues remotely via telephone and online chat portals.
- Built responsive web apps
- · Worked with a team to effectively work on projects timeline and utilize available resources.

Real Estate Intern

Kola Akomolede & Co – Victoria Island, Lagos | July 2019 - December 2019

- Advised clients on mortgage and housing conditions to identify successful properties and promote customer satisfaction.
- Liaised between property owners and prospective buyers to facilitate purchase and transfer of ownership.
- · Worked closely with clients to facilitate appropriate loans, inspections and credit reports.
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Developed real estate agents into high-powered sales professionals with skilled leadership.

Developer

Pertinence LTD - Lekki, Lagos | September 2019 - October 2019

• Qualified and competed in the first Realkathon 2019 organized by Pertinence LTD.

EDUCATION

BSc Estate Management

University of Lagos | Akoka, Lagos | November 2021

High school Diploma

International school, University of Lagos | Akoka, Lagos | September 2013